aimini.com 2005-11-24

# aimini P2P software, Building Your Own P2P Sharing World! - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

* * *

Your trust is extremely important to us and we make every effort necessary to protect your privacy. We will never sell, rent or give away any customer or client information that may be collected. 

**What about cookies?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The aimini.com does not utilize cookies on this site.

However, some of our partners sites may use cookies and therefore you should review their privacy policies. For example, The Registration company are used only to identify the customer, not to identify any specific customer traits. These cookies do not store sensitive data. This enables a more pleasant shopping experience with registration companies every time you shop with us.

The aimini.com does not have access to any of your customer information that you provide to registration company. For customers, this means that the 3rd party credit card processor only has access to your information for processing purposes only.  

**What information does Registration companies collect? How do they use it?**

When you order a product, Registration companies collects the purchaser's name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows them to process and fulfill orders and provide notification of the order status.  

**How do 3rd party credit card processors protect customer information?**

Customers who buy through the aimini.com are shopping on a secure server hosted by Registration companies that encrypts all of the customer's personal information including name, address and credit card number. Encryption ensures that no one can access or use personal information in an unauthorized manner.

The aimini.com NEVER gets the credit card number you provide at the Product Order Form. The Registration company you?e used to register an our product is fully responsible for handling the credit card or any other money transfer.

Please review the privacy policy for our 3rd party credit card processor:  [Share-it!](http://www.shareit.com/privacy_statement.html).

**Linked web sites.**

We may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

Questions or comments can be directed to [webmaster@aimini.com](mailto:webmaster@aimini.com)
